It started out at the tables in the middle of the
day Watching how the heavy world just gets in the
way We didn't bring the pity, we didn't bring the
noise Just a steady kind of quiet and a grounded
poise The guardians were watching every single
move we made But we stood inside the center and we
never were afraid We learned the tactile
language We learned the silent signs We proved
that we could operate between the hardest lines
waiting for the double tap to let us know it's
green the safest new addition to the ultimate
machine we got the clearance we made it through
the gate a pair of safe variables altering the
fate we bypassed the We are the only ones that
they will ever let inside
Yeah, we got the clearance. Now we're sleeping
on the mat right in the middle of the floor with
the husky standing guard right outside the
bedroom door. I'm arguing with Echo, and I'm
holding my ground. The most chaotic,
beautiful, and dedicated sound. We know how to
hold the space. When the system overloads We are
the trusted drivers On the album all around We
learn the tactile language We learn the silent
signs We prove that we could operate Between the
hardest lines Waiting for the double tap to let
us know it's green the safest new addition to the
ultimate machine we got the clearance we made it
through the gate a pair of safe variables
altering the fate we bypassed We passed the
firewall, we passed the final test. Welcome to
the sanctuary, welcome to the nest. When the
heavy doors are closing and the system starts to
spin, we are the only
ones that they will ever let inside. Yeah, we got
the clearance. No judgment in the room. No
pressure in the air. Just an absolute devotion
and a promise to be there We are standing on the
front lines Shoulder to shoulder now We are in
the sacred trust And we are honoring the vow
you
We got the clearance. We made it through the
gate. A pair of safe variables altering the
fate. We bypassed the firewall. We passed the
final test. Welcome to the sanctuary. Welcome
to the night.
I say ferry up, all this double tap is green. We
got the clearance.